slalom.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy | Slalom

Slalom, LLC, dba Slalom Consulting, and its subsidiaries (as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006) (" **we** " or " **us** ") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our Terms of Use, Cookies Policy and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting www.slalom.com and other websites operated by us (" **our site** ") you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.  When you contact us, or make an inquiry, via our site, your data will be collected and controlled by Slalom, LLC (a US limited liability company organized under the laws of the State of Colorado and based at 821 2nd Avenue, Suite 1900, Seattle, WA 98104) who will share that data with the relevant Slalom company to which your inquiry, or request, relates (" **Relevant Slalom Company** "). For example, if you inquire about an employment opportunity relating to Slalom Consulting Limited (a UK incorporated company) then your personal data may be shared with Slalom Consulting Limited for these purposes. In such event both Slalom, LLC and the Relevant Slalom Company may be considered controllers of your data under applicable law (for example, the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 and its implementing national legislation and the Data Protection Act 2018 (the “ **Privacy Legislation** ”)). We and the Relevant Slalom Company may also share your personal data with our other subsidiaries from time to time for the purposes set out in this privacy policy.

### For your information:

  * inquiries relating to our European business are generally handled by Slalom Consulting Limited, a company incorporated and registered in England and Wales with company number 08874662 whose registered office is at One New Change, London, EC4M 9AF;
  * inquiries relating to our Canadian business are generally handled by Slalom Consulting ULC, a Canadian unlimited liability company formed under the laws of British Columbia whose registered office is at 745 Thurlow Street, Suite 2400, Vancouver, BC V6E 0C5;
  * inquiries relating to our U.S. business are generally handled by Slalom, LLC, a limited liability company organized under the laws of the State of Colorado and based at 821 2nd Avenue, Suite 1900, Seattle, WA 98104,

unless we notify you otherwise.

## Information we collect from you

We will collect and process the following data about you:

  * **Information you give to us.**  This is information about you that you give us by filling in forms on our site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. It includes information you provide when you respond to job postings on our site, or request information about our services, and when you report a problem with our site.

The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, and other information that you voluntarily provide.

  * **Information we collect about you.**  With regard to each of your visits to our site we will automatically collect the following information: 
    * technical information, including the domain and host name from which you access the Internet, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, browser type and version, time zone and country setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
    * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), services you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.
  * **Information we receive from other sources.**  We are working closely with third parties (including, for example, marketing services and recruitment agencies) that may provide us with additional information about you.

## Cookies

Our site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our site and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy.

## Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * **Information you give to us.**  We will use this information: 
    * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
    * to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or inquired about;
    * to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. We will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you, or where you have consented to this, or where we can otherwise lawfully do so.
    * to notify you about changes to our service;
    * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * **Information we collect about you.**  We will use this information: 
    * to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
    * to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
    * as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
    * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
    * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.
  * **Information we receive from other sources.**  We will combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We will use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

## Disclosure of your information

You agree that we have the right to share your personal information with:

  * Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries.
  * Selected third parties including: 
    * service providers with which we have an agreement. These third-party service providers assist us in assessing our information security controls, maintaining our site, analyzing our site traffic, and in providing services and information to us and to users of our site;
    * advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant advertisements to you and others. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers and advertising networks, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users. We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target;
    * analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our site;

We will also disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Slalom, LLC or its subsidiaries, or substantially all of the assets of any of the foregoing, is acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Slalom, LLC or its subsidiaries, our customers, or others.

If you divulge information in a public forum offered on our site such as a chat room, message board and/or news group, this will be considered public information and may be disclosed and used by third parties.

## Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you will be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It will also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers or at our third party data centers.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

### How long we keep your information:

We retain personal data for five years. We may also retain aggregate information beyond this time for research purposes and to help us develop and improve our services. You cannot be identified from aggregate information retained or used for these purposes.

## Your rights

Depending on where you are located, you may have the right, under law, in certain circumstances:

  * to be provided with a copy of your personal data held by us;
  * to request the rectification or erasure of your personal data held by us;
  * to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data (while we verify or investigate your concerns with this information, for example);
  * to object to the further processing of your personal data, including the right to object to marketing;
  * to request that your provided personal data be moved to a third party.

Where the processing of your personal information by us is based on consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent without detriment at any time by contacting us at [privacy@slalom.com](mailto:%20privacy@slalom.com).

You can also exercise the rights listed above at any time by contacting us at [privacy@slalom.com](mailto:%20privacy@slalom.com).

If your request or concern is not satisfactorily resolved by us, you may approach your local data protection authority,

(see <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.html>).

The Information Commissioner is the supervisory authority in the UK and can provide further information about your rights and our obligations in relation to your personal data, as well as deal with any complaints that you have about our processing of your personal data.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Changes to our privacy policy

We may modify this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and will be effective as of the date of publication (which will also be noted on our website).  This policy was last updated in May 2018.

## Contact

Questions, comments or requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [privacy@slalom.com](mailto:%20privacy@slalom.com) or by mail at Slalom Consulting, Privacy Office, 821 2nd Avenue, Suite 1900, Seattle, WA 98104.
